xvideoshits.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - XVIDEOS HITS

## WATCH FREE PORN VIDEOS

## WATCH FREE PORN VIDEOS

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on www.xvideoshits.com

The security of your Data is very important to www.xvideoshits.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

##### DATA COLLECTED

Personal Information:  
Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However the visitor’s IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.  
Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.  
Cookies: When you visit www.xvideoshits.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. www.xvideoshits.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site’s features may not function properly.  
Log File Information: When you visit www.xvideoshits.com, our servers may automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.  
Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

##### USES

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. www.xvideoshits.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to www.xvideoshits.com and you do so at your own risk.

##### YOUR RIGHTS

You are entitled to access and correct your Data by doing so directly on the website or by requesting us to do so via the Contact us section.
